gameslikefinder.com 2019-08-08

# Games Finder - Privacy Policy

Read the Games Finder (“Company” or “We”) privacy policy to understand the how and what around your private information as you browse our website. Privacy is an important topic and we’re committed to being transparent in how we manage and protect your private information as a valued visitor. This privacy policy is applied consistently across the Games Finder website available at [https://gameslikefinder.com](https://gameslikefinder.com/) for any applicable services which you engage with us.

These services include but are not limited to providing video game recommendations and collecting voting on specific game titles. The privacy policy below describes the type of information obtained from you during the provision of these services and the measures in place throughout the collection, use and protection of that information.

 **What visitor information do we collect and why?**

Games Finder endeavours to keep information collected a minimum level to ensure we can operate a functional and effective website. We collect your IP address from you when you browse our website which is retained in our log files, access is limited to our hosting provider and the Games Finder administrator. Additionally certain actions will trigger additional information collection, should you not wish for this information to be collected you should avoid in engaging in activities that trigger such collection.

The triggers and information collected include:

  1.     1. Leaving a comment on an editorial review (entered text, name, email and IP address).
    2. Casting a user vote on an editorial review (user rating and IP address).
    3. Using the contact form on our contact page (entered text, name and email).

We have deemed this information necessary to obtain to ensure our website is fit for purpose while also preventing spamming of our services and thus protect the integrity of our user rating function in particular. Information from the above is retained indefinitely to allow us to better cater our user experience to your future visits and that of other visitors. Should you wish for us to remove text that is publicly available on our website that you have created you can submit a request through our contact page and we will assist you in erasing it.

Site traffic tracking utilises Google Analytics (via Google Analytic default cookies) with IP Anonymisation active, data is retained for 26 months. The data within Google Analytics maybe shared with other parties to allow us to analyse our traffic data and provide usable insights.

Amazon, a third party, uses cookies to collect information. We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. We have no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

 **What measures are in place to protect user information?**

We implement security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Additionally access to your information is limited to certain staff members to ensure access to your information is limited to only those that need it as part of their job description.

 **What about cookies?**

Yes, like other websites Games Finder does use cookies, these small files allow our website to recognise you and your browser to capture and most importantly remember key information to help the user experience. Depending on your own settings these cookies may be retained on your computer and within your browser for a range of timeframes.

Cookies are also used in advertisements, aggregation of data and recording of site interaction (such as leaving a user rating).

 **Disclosure of information to third parties**

We do not engage in selling, swapping or other activities with third parties for your personal information and data. However, we do use a number of trusted third parties who provide assistance in offering a functional website experience or other business services. Outside of these trusted parties information will only be released where we believe there is a justifiable reason under the law or in protection of our own rights or others.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. Visitors of our website should be aware that at times we may receive compensation for any traffic, leads or related sales that we provide to these third parties. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback in regard to third party links.

 **Website Content**

While Games Finder has an in house team of writers we do also accept reviews and game related imagery from third parties (freelancer writers, readers of our websites and others). We do our best to ensure that the user has permission to claim the image, text or other media as their own but we cannot make a guarantee. If you believe your rights are being impacted by imagery, text or other media displayed on our website please do not hesitate to contact us for immediate removal.

Our website automatically pulls related videos from YouTube, to prevent your videos from appearing across our website we recommend that you disable embedding in your YouTube profile or contact us directly.

The administrative team of the website is not responsible for any infringements by these third parties. We take copyright claims seriously and will act immediately on such issues when notified.

All media items on our website are used according to a Fair Use policy and are used for identification and review purposes. Some imagery is provided by relevant publisher media departments.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the privacy policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 10 March 2019

Please direct all enquiries to https://gameslikefinder.com/contact
